{"surveys":[{"id":1,"name":"NPS","content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answers":["1 Not at all likely","2","3","4","5","6","7","8","9","10 Highly likley"]}]}},{"id":2,"name":"Employee Satisfaction","content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answers":["Very unsatisfied","Unsatisied","Neutral","Satisfied","Very satisfied"]}]}},{"id":3,"name":"Lunch Order","content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answers":["Pizza","Sandwiches","Sushi","Tacos"]}]}}],"responses":[{"id":446994914831,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4"}]},"completed":"2022-01-23T00:04:58.922Z"},{"id":250940509236,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4"}]},"completed":"2022-01-23T00:04:59.622Z"},{"id":39280321619,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4"}]},"completed":"2022-01-23T00:05:00.102Z"},{"id":446966470617,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4"}]},"completed":"2022-01-23T00:08:02.134Z"},{"id":679557826795,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4"}]},"completed":"2022-01-23T00:08:03.395Z"},{"id":568195564342,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"3"}]},"completed":"2022-01-23T15:01:18.842Z"},{"id":593211404364,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answer":"Neutral"}]},"completed":"2022-01-23T17:53:26.708Z"},{"id":17921369541,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answer":"Neutral"}]},"completed":"2022-01-23T17:53:28.530Z"}],"counters":[{"id":1,"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","content":[{"response":"1 Not at all likely","counter":0},{"response":"2","counter":0},{"response":"3","counter":6},{"response":"4","counter":20},{"response":"5","counter":0},{"response":"6","counter":0},{"response":"7","counter":0},{"response":"8","counter":0},{"response":"9","counter":0},{"response":"10 Highly likley","counter":0}]},{"id":2,"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","content":[{"response":"Very unsatisfied","counter":0},{"response":"Unsatisied","counter":0},{"response":"Neutral","counter":2},{"response":"Satisfied","counter":0},{"response":"Very Satisfied","counter":0}]},{"id":3,"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","content":[{"response":"Pizza","counter":0},{"response":"Sandwiches","counter":3},{"response":"Sushi","counter":0},{"response":"Satisfied","counter":0}]}]}
